{
  "id": "flashcard-english-5-unit-12",
  "title": "Tiếng Anh Lớp 5 - Unit 12",
  "subject": "english",
  "tags": [
    "english-5",
    "unit12",
    "vocab"
  ],
  "description": "Từ vựng Unit 12: Our Tet holiday",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "pretty",
      "answer": "xinh đẹp",
      "speak": "pretty"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "peach",
      "answer": "quả đào",
      "speak": "peach"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "blossom",
      "answer": "hoa",
      "speak": "blossom"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "branch",
      "answer": "cành cây",
      "speak": "branch"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "luck",
      "answer": "may mắn",
      "speak": "luck"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "decorate",
      "answer": "trang trí",
      "speak": "decorate"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "spring roll",
      "answer": "chả giò, nem rán",
      "speak": "spring roll"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "rose",
      "answer": "hoa hồng",
      "speak": "rose"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "grandparents",
      "answer": "ông bà",
      "speak": "grandparents"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "firework",
      "answer": "pháo hoa",
      "speak": "firework"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "festival",
      "answer": "lễ hội",
      "speak": "festival"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "wear",
      "answer": "mặc, đeo",
      "speak": "wear"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "clothes",
      "answer": "quần áo",
      "speak": "clothes"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "clean",
      "answer": "sạch sẽ",
      "speak": "clean"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "excited",
      "answer": "phấn khích, hào hứng",
      "speak": "excited"
    }
  ]
}